const DATA = [
{
	question: "Which of the following is true about actively or passively managed funds?",
	answer: [
	'On average actively managed funds tend to outperform the stock market, such as the S&P500.',
	'Passive index funds experience minimal stock trades for a lower cost, but tend to underperform actively managed funds.',
	'Passive index funds outperform the majority of actively managed funds in the long-term.',
	'Passive index funds may outperform actively managed funds, but not often in the long-term.'
	],
	correctAnswer: 'Passive index funds outperform the majority of actively managed funds in the long-term.'
},

{
	question: "Several studies have repeatabled demonstrated how actively managed funds perform compared to the S&P500 after three, four, five years or more. Which is the closest figure?",
	answer:[
	'Less than 10%, but more than zero of actively managed funds continue to outperform the market.',
	'Less than 15%, but more than 10% of actively managed funds continue to outperform the market.',
	'Less than 20%, but more than 25% of actively managed funds continue to outperform the market.',
	'Less than 25%, but more than 20% of actively managed funds continue to outperform the market.'
	],
	correctAnswer: 'Less than 10%, but more than zero of actively managed funds continue to outperform the market.'
},

{
	question: "Historically, what factor has the greatest postive impact on an investor's portfolio return?",
	answer:[
	'Active management of portfolio funds',
	'Asset allocation',
	'Low fees',
	'High ratio of growth stocks'
	],
	correctAnswer: 'Asset allocation'
},

{
	question: "In long-term studies of five plus years, approximately what percent of a portfolio's return is driven by asset allocation as opposed to individual stock picks? E.g., Choosing between Google, Apple, Exxon, Wells Fargo, or GE in your portfolio vs the overall weight of each industry in your portfolio (tech, energy, consumer staples, healthcare, etc.)",
	answer:[
	'Asset allocation accounts for more than 85% of the total return',
	'Asset allocation accounts for more than 75% of the total return, but less than 85%',
	'Asset allocation accounts for more than 65% of the total return, but less than 75%',
	'Asset allocation accounts for more than 50% of the total return, but less than 65%'
	],
	correctAnswer: 'Asset allocation accounts for more than 85% of the total return'
},

{
	question: "Is paying off your mortgage generally a good idea? Select the best answer:",
	answer:[
	'Yes, a significant amount of cash can be saved from interest by repaying the loan sooner.',
	'Yes, the cash could be invested elsewhere instead of paying interest, which amounts to paying almost double for the house over the life of the loan.',
	'No, the paid interest can be used to reduce your taxes.',
	'No, when interest rates are low, investing the cash into the market will more than compensate for the interest paid.'
	],
	correctAnswer: 'No, when interest rates are low, investing the cash into the market will more than compensate for the interest paid.'
},

{
	question: "Which is an easy method that would most clearly indicate an overvalued housing market?",
	answer:[
	'When the net cash flows of renting are much less than owning.',
	'When the sale price greatly exceeds the tax valuation.',
	'When mortgage rates are excessively high.',
	'When the sale price exceeds the insurable value.'
	],
	correctAnswer: 'When the net cash flows of renting are much less than owning.'
},

{
	question: "Which would be the most advantageous reason to use a Roth IRA over a Traditional IRA?",
	answer:[
	'When you\'re in a high tax bracket, but plan to retire in a lower tax bracket',
	'When you\'re in a low tax bracket, but plan to retire in a higher tax bracket',
	'Any time as it will help reduce your taxes for the year it is funded.',
	'When you plan to retire early.'
	],
	correctAnswer: 'When you\'re in a low tax bracket, but plan to retire in a higher tax bracket'
},

{
	question: "In the Capital Asset Pricing Model, CAPM = risk-free rate + (beta)(market risk premium), what is the market risk premium?",
	answer:[
	'Expected market return less beta.',
	'Expected market return less the risk-free rate.',
	'Risk-free rate times the expected market return.',
	'None of the above.'
	],
	correctAnswer: 'Expected market return less the risk-free rate.'
},

{
	question: "The equity multiplier an indicator of a company's:",
	answer:[
	'Leverage',
	'Profitability',
	'Cash Flow',
	'Growth Rate'
	],
	correctAnswer: 'Leverage'
},

{
	question: "In what situation should you expect the Current Ratio to be less than 1.0?",
	answer:[
	'When a company is holding more cash than it owes in current liabilities',
	'When a company has long credit periods for payables and high receivables turnover.',
	'When a company maintains low payables to current assets.',
	'When a company maintains high receivables relative to payables.'
	],
	correctAnswer: 'When a company has long credit periods for payables and high receivables turnover.'
},

];
